code4share.net 2014-12-16

# Privacy Policy | Code 4 Share | Thousands of resources for free download

**Privacy Policy**

Code4Share.Net created this privacy statement to illustrate our company commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information collecting and cookies for Code4Share.Net.

 **Collecting of Personally-Identifying Information**  
When a visitor joins Code4Share.Net as our member, certain personality-identifying information is requested. For example, username, email address, website name and website URL. Code4Share.Net collects such information just to fulfill the purpose of visitor's interaction and shall never sell or trade such information with others. Code4Share.Net discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Code4Share.Net believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of www.Code4Share.Net, third parties, or the public at large. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

 **Cookies**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Code4Share.Net uses cookies to help Code4Share.Net identify and track visitors, their usage of www.get-simple.info website, and their website access preferences. Visitors can set browsers to refuse cookies place on their computers, but certain features of Code4Share.Net may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

 **Ads**  
Advertising partners may set cookies when their ads appeared on Code4Share.Net to allow ad server to recognize your computer. The aim of these cookies is to illustrate targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Code4Share.Net and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Security**  
To protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control, log file access is restricted to system administrators only once stored on Code4Share.Net server.

 **Contact Information**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, please contact us at info[at]code4share.net. 

#### Register with facebook

#### Already have an account?

__Login now

**Please use "Search function" before submit request!**

**Enter your Email or Username**
